{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Children! _______ a noise!",
      "a": "You stop making",
      "b": "Stop making",
      "c": "Stop to make",
      "d": "Stop you making",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Look, Chris is waiting for you. Well, ______ wait!",
      "a": "let she",
      "b": "let her",
      "c": "you let she",
      "d": "you let her",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mark, _______ take a taxi. It's too expensive!",
      "a": "don't",
      "b": "you don't",
      "c": "don't let you",
      "d": "you not",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tell Sarah I want to see her _______ to see me.",
      "a": "Let her come",
      "b": "Let her to come",
      "c": "You let her come",
      "d": "Let she come",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "You have to fill in the forms. Well, ______ fill them in!",
      "a": "we let's",
      "b": "let's",
      "c": "let's we",
      "d": "we let us",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Olivia is already doing it. OK,_______ do it!",
      "a": "you let her",
      "b": "let her",
      "c": "let you",
      "d": "let she",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am thirsty. ' Yes,_______ some water.'",
      "a": "let's drink",
      "b": "let we drink",
      "c": "drink you",
      "d": "you drink",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Come on Helen, _______ peace.",
      "a": "we make",
      "b": "make us",
      "c": "let's make",
      "d": "let make",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The children want to go out. OK,_______ go out!",
      "a": "let them",
      "b": "let they",
      "c": "you let them",
      "d": "you let they",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Now,______ forget that we've got to win today!",
      "a": "let's no",
      "b": "let's not",
      "c": "don't let we",
      "d": "don't we",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me...Â \n+ Let somebody do something \n+ Negative form: Let somebody not do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}